<DialogueTree>
  <DialogueNode>
    <Name>Curator13</Name>
    <Dialogue>
      <Page>Was there something you needed?</Page>
    </Dialogue>
    <DialogueOptionsList>
      <DialogueOption>
        <Text>Anything else you need me to do before I launch?</Text>
        <DialogueTarget>CuratorAcetateIntroFirstLoop</DialogueTarget>
      </DialogueOption>
    </DialogueOptionsList>
  </DialogueNode>
  
  <DialogueNode>
		<Name>CuratorAcetateIntroFirstLoop</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Hmmm. There was one thing that I wanted to ask you about. I wasn't going to mention it since this is your first expedition, but considering all of the other travelers are currently preoccupied or are entirely unhelpful, I suppose now is as much of an appropriate time as any.</Page>
			<Page>A bit before your time, and before Feldspar went missing, there was another traveler. A Hatchling. Quite like you, in fact.</Page>
			<Page>They were one of the first of the new generation of Outer Wilds Ventures that came after of the four of us - that being me, Slate, Gossan, and of course Feldspar. They were quite taken with the name "Acetate" of all things, something that was of their own invention by the way, but I have never seen a traveller so enamored with the Hearthian spirit as they were.</Page>
			<Page>That is, of course, until one day - even more suddenly than Feldspar - they went out to the edge of the solar system and just... disappeared. No one knows why. With Feldspar I expected it, as much as I hate to admit, but with Acetate... I can't even begin to imagine how that would happen.</Page>
			<Page>Could you find out what happened to them for me? I know that it's a big ask, but if you at some point find anything that could give us - or me - some closure, I would greatly appreciate it.</Page>
		</Dialogue>
	  <DialogueOptionsList>
		  <DialogueOption>
			  <Text>Where should I start?</Text>
			  <DialogueTarget>CuratorAcetate_Attlerock</DialogueTarget>
		  </DialogueOption>
	  </DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>
	
	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>CuratorAcetate_Attlerock</Name>
		<RevealFacts>
			<FactID>TH_DEEP_SPACE_HORNFELS</FactID>
		</RevealFacts>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>The last place that they went to before they went missing was the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Lunar Outpost</color>]]>, on the Attlerock. We don't use it much anymore, but back in the day it was vital for the exploration of our solar system.</Page>
			<Page>I'd ask Esker if they remember anything about it, on the off chance that they do. It seems to me that there aren't really any leads as to where Acetate could have gone, unfortunately, and I don't necessarily expect for you to find anything useful on your own.</Page>
			<Page>Still though, it's nice to get a new set of eyes on it after all of these years. It's hard to get over the guilt of something terrible happening to someone under your watch, especially when I was the one who encouraged them to become an astronaut in the first place.</Page>
			<Page>Anyhow, don't let me keep you. I'm sure you're just itching to get back to your expedition!</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		<DialogueTarget>Curator13</DialogueTarget>
	</DialogueNode>

</DialogueTree>