<DialogueTree>
	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>Esker1</Name>
		<DialogueOptionsList>
			<DialogueOption>
				<RequiredLogCondition>TH_DEEP_SPACE_HORNFELS</RequiredLogCondition>
				<Text>Do you know anything about Acetate?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>Acetate_Start</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>Esker2</Name>
		<DialogueOptionsList>
			<DialogueOption>
				<RequiredLogCondition>TH_DEEP_SPACE_HORNFELS</RequiredLogCondition>
				<Text>Do you know anything about Acetate?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>Acetate_Start</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>

	<!--DIVERGENCE-->
	
	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>Acetate_Start</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Acetate, huh? <![CDATA[<Pause/>]]>Now that's a name that I haven't heard in a very, <![CDATA[<i>]]>very<![CDATA[</i>]]> long time.</Page>
			<Page>Well, as a matter of fact, Acetate was the last member of Outer Wilds Ventures to actually use this outpost. Also part of the reason that we stopped, too. <![CDATA[<Pause/>]]><![CDATA[<color=grey>Sigh...</color>]]> A real Feldspar, that one.</Page>
			<Page><![CDATA[<i>]]>Incredibly<![CDATA[</i>]]> smart, though. A little too much, if you ask me. I suppose that's why Hornfels is still so hung up on it after all of these years. Someone like that doesn't really <![CDATA[<i>]]>go<![CDATA[</i>]]> missing.</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		<DialogueOptionsList>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>Do you have any idea where they could have gone?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>AcetateSatellite</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>AcetateSatellite</Name>
		<RevealFacts>
			<FactID>TH_DEEP_SPACE_ACETATE</FactID>
		</RevealFacts>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Not really. The travelers don't really tell me those sorts of things anymore. <![CDATA[<size=20>]]>Not that they ever did.<![CDATA[</size>]]> Frankly Acetate could have ended up anywhere by now.</Page>
			<Page>I do remember hearing that they wanted to do something before they cut themselves loose. Something about scouting a good location for Hornfels' <![CDATA[<color=orange>Deep Space Satellite</color>]]>, I forget the details. Don't know what happened to them after that.</Page>
			<Page>Was that helpful? Honestly you probably know more about this whole thing than I do at this point. Good luck on the search, though! Hope you find them.</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		<DialogueTarget>Esker2</DialogueTarget>
	</DialogueNode>

</DialogueTree>